Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals
1936-1994
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.2
20 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 2 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1990s, UE.4.1.2, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 2 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals in New England and are now part of the UE's Northeast Region. This series contains files on UE District 2 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 2. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 2 Records, 1950s-1980s, UE.15.2, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 219 Records, 1980s-1990s, UE.16.219, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 223 Records, 1970s-1980s, UE.16.223, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 274 Records, 1940s-1992, UE.16.274, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 277 Records, 1980s, UE.16.277, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 284 Records, 1970s-1990s, UE.16.284, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 291 Records, 1970s-1980s, UE.16.291, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 299 Records, 1980s-1990s, UE.16.299, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- New England -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- New England -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Labor; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 2; Matles, James J.; Emspak, Julius
- District 2, 1.
  - District 2 Local Actions, January 30-February 20, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 2 Constitution, April 13, 1944-November 6, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - District 2 Constitution, April 1943-April 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 2 Council Directory, November 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 2 President Paul Seymour, June 14, 1949-December 3, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Paul Seymour to All Springfield and Holyoke Locals, June 14, 1949; 1.
    - Seymour to UE Members Regarding Taft-Hartley and Unemployment with "Know the Score" Card, June 14, 1949; 2.
    - Seymour to All Locals Regarding Local 262 Keystone Strike with The Keystone Story, August 16, 1949; 3.
    - Seymour to All District 2 Locals Regarding Factionalism, September 27, 1949; 4.
    - Seymour to UE Members Regarding 1949 UE Convention and Factionalism with Statement on Collective Bargaining, Statement of UE General Executive Board and Duties and Privileges of Membership, 5.
    - Seymour to All District 2 Staff Members Regarding Finances, April 27, 1953; 6.
    - Seymour to District 2 Staff Regarding Finances, May 14, 1953; 7.
    - Seymour to UE Regarding Bridgeport-New Haven Conference, May 28, 1953; 8.
    - Seymour to All District 2 Staff Members Regarding National Labor Relations Board, September 1, 1953; 9.
    - Seymour to All UE District 2 Locals Regarding Local 299 Bradley Laboratories Strike, November 6, 1956; 10.
    - Seymour to All District 2 Locals Regarding Local 271 Turner Tanning Strike, November 6, 1956; 11.
    - Seymour to All District 2 Locals Regarding Local 259 Cescco Container and Local 299 Bradley Laboratories Strikes, December 3, 1956; 12.
    - Seymour Letter Regarding Address Change, 13.
  - District 2 President Paul Seymour, January 18, 1956-September 27, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 2 President Paul Seymour, December 1, 1960-December 27, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 2 President Paul Seymour, January 16, 1964-August 4, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - District 2 President James M. Kane, October 20, 1971-March 4, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 2 Boston Council Meetings, October 11, 1957-August 11, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - District 2 Council Minutes, May 9, 1942-May 18,1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - District Council Minutes, May 9, 1942; 1.
    - District Council Minutes with District 2 Constitutional Amendments, Attendance, Ellsworth Grant Speech, and Reports of Veterans, War Labor Board Resolution, Public Affairs, and Press and Public Relations Panels, May 18, 1945; 2.
  - District 2 Council Minutes with District 2 Constitutional Amendments, Attendance, Ellsworth Grant Speech, and Reports of Veterans, War Labor Board Resolution, Public Affairs, and Press and Public Relations Panels, May 18, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - District 2 Council Minutes with Russ Nixon Report, Local 262 Veterans Committee Resolution, Trustees Report, Attendance and Statements by Oliver Arsenault, Josephine Willard, Charles Klim Kowski, Albert Smith, Michael Berescik, Albert Fitzgerald, April 11, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - District 2 Council Minutes with Report and Recommendations of Appeals Committee, Roll Call Votes and Attendance, June 21, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - District 2 Council Minutes, July 18-October 12, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - District Council Minutes with Resolutions Regarding Housing, Wages, House Un-American Activities Committee, Factionalism, Political Action, Machine Tool Industry, and Foreign Policy; David Scribner, Political Action, and Trustees Reports; and Attendance List, July 18, 1947; 1.
    - District Council Minutes with Attendance, October 12, 1947; 2.
  - District 2 Council Minutes, January 10-April 17, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - District Council Minutes with Trustees Report, Paul Seymour Letter to Harold Senior and Attendance, January 10, 1948; 1.
    - District Council Minutes with Trustees Report; Resolution Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry; April 19, 1948, Seymour Letter to Philip Murray Regarding UAW Inter-union Rivalry; and Attendance, April 17, 1948; 2.
  - District 2 Council Minutes with Trustees Report; Resolutions on Wages, Unemployment, and Social and Labor Legislation; Roll Call and Attendance; and Memoranda on Trustees Report and Unemployment Compensation, January 15, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - District 2 Council Minutes, April 9-July 8, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - District Council Minutes with Locals in Attendance and Trustees, Wages, Unemployment, Legislation, and James Matles Reports, April 9, 1949; 1.
    - District Council Minutes with Trustees Report; Support of GE Negotiating Committee; Remarks of Secretary-Treasurer Julius Emspak; Resolution on Wages; July 7, 1949, Joseph Dermody Letter to All General Electric Locals Regarding Factionalism; Summary of David Scribner Report Regarding Factionalism; June 9, 1949, WBRK Six O'Clock Newscast Script; and Attendance List of Locals, July 8, 1949; 2.
  - District 2 Council Minutes, October 29, 1949-October 20, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - District Council Minutes with Trustees Report, October 29, 1949; 1.
    - District Council Minutes with Financial Report and Attendance, October 15, 1950; 2.
    - District Council Minutes with Financial Report, October 20, 1951; 3.
  - District 2 Council Minutes, January 14, 1983-February 20, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 2 Council Resolutions, June 16, 1942-April 9, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Resolution Regarding John L. Lewis and Foreign Policy, June 16, 1942; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Victory Program, June 16, 1942; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Harry Bridges Deportation, June 16, 1942; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Racism, June 16, 1942; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Inflation, June 16, 1942; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Anglo-Soviet Trade Union Committee, June 16, 1942; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Second Front, June 16, 1942; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Women, June 16, 1942; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Civilian Conservation Corps and National Youth Administration, June 16, 1942; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Win the War Labor Conference, June 16, 1942; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Reconversion, August 14, 1945; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions with Paul Seymour Letter, November 25, 1945; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding Unemployment, April 9, 1949; 13.
    - Resolution Regarding Old Age Pensions, April 9, 1949; 14.
    - Resolution Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 9, 1949; 15.
    - Resolution Regarding Full Employment, April 9, 1949; 16.
    - Resolution Regarding UE Policy and Factionalism, April 9, 1949; 17.
  - District 2 Executive Council Resolution Regarding Political Action with January 29, 1948, Paul Seymour Letter to All Locals, January 28, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 2 Staff Meeting Minutes, June 18-July 15, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 2 Connecticut Reports, September-December 1943 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Report with October 21, 1943, Charles Rivers Letter to Julius Emspak, September 1943; 1.
    - Reports, October-December 1943; 2-3.
  - District 2 Connecticut Reports, January-August 1944 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Report, January 1944; 1.
    - Report with Joseph Adams Letter to All United Auto Workers, UE and United Steelworkers of America Locals, May-June 1944; 2.
    - Report, July-August 1944; 3.
  - District 2 Northern New England Reports, July-November 1944 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 2 Eastern Massachusetts Staff Meetings, December 6, 1943-January 3, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 2 Connecticut Staff Meetings, June 3-December 22, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Meeting with June 8, 1944, Charles Rivers Letter to Julius Emspak, June 3, 1944; 1.
    - Meeting with August 21, 1944, Rivers Letter to Emspak, August 18, 1944; 2.
    - Meeting with January 16, 1945, Hugh Harley Letter to Emspak, December 22, 1944; 3.
  - District 2 Federal Mediation and Conciliation Services Committee Report, January 26, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 2 Disposition of Connecticut UE Staff, September 21, 1944-October 1, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 2 Disposition of Massachusetts Staff, October 1945-December 1947 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - District 2 Staff Meeting Minutes, December 11, 1943-November 5, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Western Massachusetts Staff Meeting, December 11, 1943; 1.
    - Bridgeport Area Report, November 18, 1944; 2.
    - Massachusetts and Rhode Island Staff Meeting, October 19, 1945; 3.
    - Hartford Report, November 5, 1945; 4.
  - District 2 Incoming George Breiner Correspondence, January 2, 1941-September 24, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Julius Emspak Telegram Regarding Local 277, December 16, 1941; 1.
    - Emspak Letter, July 24, 1942; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, August 7-21, 1942; 3-4.
    - Nat Geller Regarding Finances, September 24, 1942; 5.
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 2, 1941; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Morse Twist Drill, Office of Production Mobilization and Unfair Labor Practices, October 31, 1941; 7.
    - Matles Regarding Organizers Report, December 12, 1941-January 14, 1942; 8-10.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 15, 1942; 11.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Staff Members, January 15, 1942; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 27-February 12, 1942; 13-15.
    - Matles Regarding Organizers Reports, March 30-April 29, 1942; 16-17.
    - Matles Regarding Morse Twist Drill Organization, April 30, 1942; 18.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members and Conscription, May 4, 1942; 19.
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, June 9, 1942; 20.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 2, 1942; 21.
  - District 2 Outgoing George Breiner Correspondence, December 15, 1941-September 10, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - George Breiner to James Matles Regarding Morse Twist Drill Organization, December 15, 1941; 1.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles Regarding Conscription, December 23, 1941; 2.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 16, 1942; 3.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Morse Twist Drill, January 16, 1942; 4.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 20, 1942; 5.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Organizers Conference, February 11, 1942; 6.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles Regarding War Labor Board, February 22, 1942; 7.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles Regarding Machine Shops and Wages, February 26, 1942; 8.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Conscription, March 9, 1942; 9.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Supplies, March 30, 1942; 10.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Publicity, March 10, 1942; 11.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles Regarding Conscription, May 9-12, 1942; 12-13.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 26, 1942; 14.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, May 26, 1942; 15.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 29, 1942; 16.
    - Breiner to Matles Regarding Address Change, September 10, 1942; 17.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles Regarding Conscription, 1942; 18.
    - Breiner Telegram to Matles, 19.
  - District 2 Incoming Matthew Campbell Correspondence, April 24, 1936-May 24, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 15, 1937; 1.
    - Barish Regarding District Constitutions, February 26, 1937; 2.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, March 8, 1937; 3.
    - Barish Regarding District 2 Locals with Secretaries and Plants of District 2, March 31, 1937; 4.
    - Barish Regarding District 2 Locals with a List of District 2 Locals, May 20, 1937; 5.
    - Barish Regarding Credentials, June 7, 1937; 6.
    - James Carey Regarding American Bosch Magneto, Bridgeport General Electric, and Sickle Coil Organization and People's Press, April 24, 1936; 7.
    - Carey Regarding Local 204, Camden RCA and Supplies, July 30, 1936; 8.
    - Carey Telegram Regarding Wages, November 19, 1936; 9.
    - Carey Regarding American Bosch Magneto and National Labor Relations Board, November 24, 1936; 10.
    - Carey Regarding Springfield Westinghouse, January 14, 1937; 11.
    - Carey Regarding District Council, Stackpole Resister and Bridgeport General Electric, January 22, 1937; 12.
    - Carey Regarding Westinghouse and Staff Members, February 18, 1937; 13.
    - Carey Telegram, February-April, 1937; 14-16.
    - Carey Regarding S.B. Lederer Strike with Carey Letter to Morris Brown and May 23, 1937, Brown Letter to Carey, May 24, 1937; 17.
  - District 2 Incoming Matthew Campbell Correspondence, April 22, 1936-May 2, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - James Carey Regarding Local 724 and Local 732 Lima, OH, Westinghouse, September 16, 1937; 1.
    - Carey Regarding Factionalism, November 25-December 5, 1940; 2-3.
    - Carey Telegram Regarding Local 251 Molloy Collective Bargaining, January 17, 1941; 4.
    - Carey Telegram Regarding Hanson Whitney Strike, May 2, 1941; 5.
    - Alice Dodge Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, October 15, 1937; 6.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Charters, April 22, 1936; 7.
    - Emspak Letter, April 29, 1936; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Bosch Magneto Sickle Coil Organization, May 11, 1936; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor, May 25, 1936; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 205, Supplies and Schenectady General Electric Strike, June 16, 1936; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies and Local 301 Schenectady General Electric Collective Bargaining, June 18, 1936; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 103 RCA, Local 106 Wirth and Local 603 Pittsburgh Meter Strikes, July 3, 1936; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Bridgeport General Electric Organization and Local 103 RCA Strike, July 18, 1936; 14.
    - Emspak Letter, August 11, 1936; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Bridgeport General Electric, August 11, 1936; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding International Association of Machinists, Federation of Metal and Allied Unions and Eisman Magneto, October 29, 1936; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Springfield Westinghouse Organization, Camden RCA National Labor Relations Board Election and Lester Westinghouse, November 10, 1936; 18.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Bosch Magneto Wages and Eisman Magneto, November 18, 1936; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Bosch Magneto and East Pittsburgh Westinghouse Organization, Schenectady General Electric NLRB Election, Bridgeport General Electric Strike and CIO, December 17, 1936; 20.
  - District 2 Incoming Matthew Campbell Correspondence, May 14, 1937-May 13, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, Organizing and Milton Bradley Strikes, May 14, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding UE Conventions, July 1, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, July 3, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 19, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 6, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Bosch Machine Tool, Providence and UE Convention, August 20, 1937; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, October 28, 1937; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 246, December 2, 1937; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Milton Bradley Strike, February 5, 1938; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 13, 1940; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 206, November 27, 1940; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Members, December 23, 1940; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 14-March 11, 1941; 13-15.
    - Emspak Regarding Local Secretaries, May 13, 1941; 16.
    - Powers Hapgood Regarding New England Congress of Industrial Organizations with New England Council CIO Financial Report, October 14, 1937; 17.
  - District 2 Incoming Matthew Campbell Correspondence, June 22, 1937-May 28, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - James Matles Regarding Organization, June 22, 1937; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Recieved Letters, September 9, 1937; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Pittsfield General Electric Unemployment, November 1, 1937; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, November 19, 1937; 4.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 20, 1937; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Chicopee Falls Westinghouse and Runaway Shops, December 29, 1937; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Springfield Westinghouse and Runaway Shops, January 6, 1938; 7.
    - Matles Regarding Rhode Island Unemployment with November 1937 State of Rhode Island Employee Report, January 8, 1938; 8.
    - Matles Regarding Bridgeport and Bryant General Electric Unemployment, January 27, 1938; 9.
    - Matles Regarding White Collar Workers, Allis Chalmers, Electric, and Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians, March 1, 1938; 10.
    - Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Aerovox, November 26, 1940; 11.
    - Matles Regarding Aerovox and Staff Members, December 16, 1940; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 18, 1940-March 7, 1941; 13-17.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, March 13, 1941; 18.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 25-May 14, 1941; 19-21.
    - Matles Regarding Connecticut Organization and Boston Staff Members, May 28, 1941; 22.
  - District 2 Incoming Matthew Campbell Correspondence, October 13-September 2, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - William Mitchell Telegram Regarding Local 206 Officers Election, October 13, 1937; 1.
    - Charles Newell Regarding Organization, District Council, Finances and Unemployment, November 14, 1937; 2.
    - George Wilson Regarding Pittsfield General Electric and Staff Members with January 2, 1941, Staff Finances, September 2, 1937; 3.
  - District 2 Outgoing Matthew Campbell Correspondence, May 11, 1936-November 24, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Matthew Campbell to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 603 Organization and American Federation of Labor, May 11, 1936; 1.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Local 301 Officers and Locals 204, 205 and 206, June 17, 1936; 2.
    - Campbell Telegram to J. Emspak Regarding Bridgeport General Electric, July 21, 1936; 3.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Local 204 and Unfair Labor Practices, July 27, 1936; 4.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding American Bosch and Wages, November 5, 1936; 5.
    - Campbell Telegram to James Carey Regarding Wages, November 19, 1936; 6.
    - Campbell to Carey Regarding Local 206 American Bosch Collective Bargaining, 1936; 7.
    - Campbell Telegram to Carey, January 25, 1937; 8.
    - Campbell to Carey Regarding Pittsfield Bridgeport General Electric Organization, February 2, 1937; 9.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 2, 1937; 10.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 7, 1937; 11.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak, June 5, 1937; 12.
    - Campbell Telegram to James Matles, June 23, 1937; 13.
    - Campbell Telegram to Stella Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Minutes, June 28, 1937; 14.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding 1937 UE Constitution, June 28, 1937; 15.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 19, 1937; 16.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Rhode Island Staff Finances and Bridgeport General Electric, August 3, 1937; 17.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Rhode Island Supplies, August 18, 1937; 18.
    - Campbell to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 14, 1937; 19.
    - Campbell to Carey Regarding Local 720 and Anti-communism, September 29, 1937; 20.
    - Campbell to Carey, October 19, 1937; 21.
    - Campbell to J. Emspak Regarding Local 246 Staff Members, November 24, 1937; 22.
  - District 2 Outgoing Matthew Campbell Correspondence, January 5, 1938-January 8, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Matthew Campbell to James Carey Regarding Chicopee Falls Westinghouse and Runaway Shops, January 5, 1938; 1.
    - Campbell to Julius Emspak Regarding Milton Bradley Strike, Unemployment, Springfield Westinghouse and American Bosch, February 4, 1938; 2.
    - Campbell to Matles Regarding Local 242, White Collar Workers, Wages and Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians, February 28, 1938; 3.
    - Campbell to Emspak Regarding Committee to Defend America, Hours and Staff Finances, January 8, 1941; 4.
    - Campbell Telegram to Carey Regarding Harson Whitney Strike, 5.
  - District 2 Incoming Paul Seymour Correspondence, July 22, 1944-November 7, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Members, July 22, 1944-February 21, 1947; 1-5.
    - Barish Regarding Local 273 and Political Action Committee, March 17, 1948; 6.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, October 28, 1948; 7.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 16, 1949; 8.
    - Barish Regarding Local 214 Keystone Strike, October 26, 1949; 9.
    - Barish Regarding Massachusetts Department of Labor, February 17, 1950; 10.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, October 3, 1950; 11.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 23, 1951; 12.
    - Barish Regarding Local 231 and Finances, June 7, 1952; 13.